export const pythonListsExercise = {
  title: 'Python Lists â€“ Exercise',
  questions: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Which brackets are used to define a list?',
      options: ['()', '{}', '[]', '<>'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'List indexing starts from?',
      options: ['-1', '0', '1', 'Any number'],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Which method adds an element at the end of a list?',
      options: ['add()', 'insert()', 'append()', 'push()'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Are lists mutable?',
      options: ['Yes', 'No', 'Sometimes', 'Never'],
      correctIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Which function gives length of a list?',
      options: ['size()', 'count()', 'length()', 'len()'],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Negative index -1 refers to?',
      options: ['First element', 'Second element', 'Last element', 'Error'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Which list is valid?',
      options: [
        '[1, 2, 3]',
        '(1, 2, 3)',
        '{1, 2, 3}',
        '<1, 2, 3>',
      ],
      correctIndex: 0,
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Which removes a specific value from list?',
      options: ['delete()', 'pop()', 'remove()', 'clear()'],
      correctIndex: 2,
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Lists can store?',
      options: ['Only numbers', 'Only strings', 'Same data types', 'Mixed data types'],
      correctIndex: 3,
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Lists are mainly used to?',
      options: [
        'Store single value',
        'Store multiple values',
        'Print output',
        'Take input',
      ],
      correctIndex: 1,
    },
  ],
}